<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
    <author>RichOPick</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
	<title>
        <en>Excess Animals Sold</en>
        <de>Überschüssige Tiere Verkauft</de>
        <pl>Sprzedano Nadmiar Zwierząt</pl>
        <ru>Лишние Животные Проданы</ru>
        <fr>Animaux Excédentaires Vendus</fr>
        <it>Animali In Eccesso Venduti</it>
        <es>Exceso De Animales Vendidos</es>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Excess Animals Sold

This mod changes animal husbandry placeables so they sell baby animals when the husbandry is full, rather than deleting them.

For example, suppose your cowshed has a capacity of 20 cows and contains 18 cows.
If 4 of those cows are ready to reproduce, then upon reproducing 2 calves will be added to the shed, and 2 calves will be sold.

Please leave feedback, requests, or bug reports on GitHub: https://github.com/richpet9/excess-animals-sold
]]>
</en>
    <de><![CDATA[Überschüssige Tiere Verkauft

Dieser Mod ändert platzierbare Tierhaltungsobjekte, sodass Tierbabys verkauft werden, wenn die Haltung voll ist, anstatt sie zu löschen.

Angenommen, Ihr Kuhstall hat eine Kapazität für 20 Kühe und beherbergt 18 Kühe.
Wenn vier dieser Kühe zur Fortpflanzung bereit sind, werden nach der Fortpflanzung zwei Kälber in den Stall gegeben und zwei Kälber verkauft.

Bitte hinterlassen Sie Feedback, Wünsche oder Fehlerberichte auf GitHub: https://github.com/richpet9/excess-animals-sold
]]>
</de>
    <pl><![CDATA[Sprzedano Nadmiar Zwierząt

Ten mod zmienia obiekty do umieszczania w hodowli zwierząt, tak aby sprzedawały młode zwierzęta, gdy hodowla jest pełna, zamiast je usuwać.

Załóżmy na przykład, że twoja obora ma pojemność 20 krów i zawiera 18 krów.
Jeśli 4 z tych krów będą gotowe do rozrodu, to po rozrodzie 2 cielęta zostaną dodane do obór, a 2 cielęta zostaną sprzedane.

Prosimy o pozostawienie opinii, próśb lub raportów o błędach w GitHub: https://github.com/richpet9/excess-animals-sold
]]>
</pl>
    <ru><![CDATA[Продано лишних животных

Этот мод изменяет размещаемые объекты животноводства, чтобы они продавали детенышей животных, когда хозяйство заполнено, а не удаляли их.

Например, предположим, что ваш коровник вмещает 20 коров и содержит 18 коров.
Если из этих коров 4 готовы к воспроизводству, то при воспроизводстве в коровник добавляются 2 теленка, а 2 теленка продаются.

Пожалуйста, оставляйте отзывы, запросы или отчеты об ошибках на GitHub: https://github.com/richpet9/excess-animals-sold.
]]>
</ru>
    <fr><![CDATA[Animaux Excédentaires Vendus

Ce mod modifie les objets d'élevage afin qu'ils vendent des bébés animaux lorsque l'élevage est plein, plutôt que de les supprimer.

Par exemple, supposons que votre étable ait une capacité de 20 vaches et contienne 18 vaches.
Si 4 de ces vaches sont prêtes à se reproduire, alors lors de la reproduction, 2 veaux seront ajoutés au hangar et 2 veaux seront vendus.

Veuillez laisser vos commentaires, demandes ou rapports de bogues sur GitHub : https://github.com/richpet9/excess-animals-sold
]]>
</fr>
    <it><![CDATA[Animali in Eccesso Venduti

Questa mod modifica i posizionamenti dell'allevamento di animali in modo da vendere cuccioli quando l'allevamento è pieno, anziché eliminarli.

Ad esempio, supponiamo che la tua stalla abbia una capacità di 20 mucche e ne contenga 18.
Se 4 di queste mucche sono pronte per riprodursi, dopo la riproduzione 2 vitelli verranno aggiunti alla stalla e 2 vitelli verranno venduti.

Si prega di lasciare feedback, richieste o segnalazioni di bug su GitHub: https://github.com/richpet9/excess-animals-sold
]]>
</it>
    <es><![CDATA[Exceso de Animales Vendidos

Este mod cambia los lugares de cría de animales para que vendan animales bebés cuando la cría esté llena, en lugar de eliminarlos.

Por ejemplo, supongamos que su establo tiene una capacidad de 20 vacas y contiene 18 vacas.
Si 4 de esas vacas están listas para reproducirse, al reproducirse se agregarán 2 terneros al cobertizo y se venderán 2 terneros.

Deje comentarios, solicitudes o informes de errores en GitHub: https://github.com/richpet9/excess-animals-sold
]]>
</es>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_fw.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="ExcessAnimalsSold.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

    <l10n>
        <text name="rp_EXCESS_ANIMALS_SOLD">
            <en>Excess animals sold</en>
            <de>Überschüssige tiere verkauft</de>
            <pl>Sprzedano nadmiar zwierząt</pl>
            <ru>Лишние животные проданы</ru>
            <fr>Animaux excédentaires vendus</fr>
            <it>Animali in eccesso venduti</it>
            <es>Exceso de animales vendidos</es>
        </text>
    </l10n>
</modDesc>
